If you want respect, you've got to take it.
You Got Served is a music, drama film directed by Chris Stokes.
Rad's Warehouse, the best hip-hop crews in Los
Angeles compete for money and respect.
But when a suburban crew crashes the party, stealing their dancers — and their moves
— two warring friends have to pull together to represent the street.
Elgin, played by Marques Houston.
David, played by Omarion.
Rico, played by J-Boog.
Rashann, played by Lil' Fizz.
Liyah, played by Jennifer Freeman.
Beautifull, played by Meagan Good.
You Got Served is a 2004 American dance drama film written and directed by Chris Stokes, who was also the business manager of
the performers who were the film's main characters: recording artist Marques Houston and the boy band B2K.
The plot follows a group of dancers who take part
in a street dancing competition.
Filming took place Between May 1, 2003, and June 25, 2003.
You Got Served was released on January 30, 2004 by Screen Gems.
The film received negative reviews from critics, and grossed
$51 million against an $8 million budget.
It was followed by a sequel, You Got Served: Beat the World (2011).
The film explores themes of dance, hip-hop, dance
performance, breakdance, musical.
The tone is emotional.